https://www.14oranges.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT14 Oranges Software Inc, (14 Oranges), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our websites and make use of our online facilities and services confidential, secure, accurate, and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with 14 Oranges of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to 14 Oranges Software Inc, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.14oranges.com, www.info-grove.com, www.metro-grove.com, infogrove.14oranges.com, metrogrove.14oranges.com, or any affiliated subdomain of 14oranges.com, (Websites),  you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.Collecting of InformationThese websites collect various types of information, such as:Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, phone number, billing and/or credit card information which may be used when you purchase our services and to deliver the services you have requested.Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies, and server logsPlease rest assured that our Websites shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of completed forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address, or type of operating system used to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service. It is highly recommend and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of, and share the information collected. Use of Information Collected14 Oranges may collect and make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and/or services and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from 14 Oranges. 14 Oranges may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.14 Oranges does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent, or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.14 Oranges may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.14 Oranges may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws, and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon 14 Oranges and/or our Websites;Maintain, safeguard, and/or preserve all the right and/or property of 14 Oranges;Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of our services and/or the general public.Children Under Age of 1314 Oranges does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.Unsubscribe or Opt-OutAll users and/or visitors to our Websites have the option to discontinue receiving communications from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe from our communications, please send an email to unsubscribe@14oranges.com requesting to be removed.Links to Other WebsitesOur Websites do contain links to affiliate and other websites. 14 Oranges does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices, and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our Websites and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our Websites.Cookies14 Oranges collects information related to your use of our Websites using cookies, web beacons, and log information.Cookies are small files containing strings of text stored on your computer. 14 Oranges may uses cookies to authenticate you as a user when you log in, track your session, deliver content specific to your preferences and interests, provide features related to payment and customer service, and provide other functions.Web beacons are objects embedded into web pages that allow us to determine whether and for how long users view web pages. We use web beacons for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, auditing and reporting, personalization, and other functions.Log information may include web requests, Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, browser language, date and time of your request, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 14 Oranges uses this information to enhance the security and functionality of our Websites and to make your access more convenient, secure, and efficient.14 Oranges also uses information gathered from logs, cookies, and web beacons to monitor website performance; improve website design, functionality, and security; and assemble web analytics and activity trends. 14 Oranges retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.You may stop your browser from accepting cookies or web beacons. The Help portion of your browser should explain how to configure your browser’s cookie handling. Your browser may have add-ons that may help you block web beacons. You may have limited functionality if you block cookies or web beacons set by our Websites.HubSpot14 Oranges uses HubSpot cookies to track our visitors and contacts in order to understand, personalize and streamline your user experience. When a user visits our Websites, HubSpot leaves behind a cookie on our visitors’ computers that helps us identify them on future visits. Through this mechanism we are able to provide tailored experiences with smart content tailored for language, pre-filled forms, and product interest. when you opt out of allowing cookies, Hubspot automatically stops tracking your computer. However, in order to comply with your preference, we’ll need to use one cookie so you are not asked to make this choice again. View links for more information on the cookies used by HubSpot and HubSpot’s Privacy Policy: http://knowledge.hubspot.com/cookies and http://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policyGoogle Analytics14 Oranges uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help us analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Policy at https://policies.google.com/privacyYou can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings at http://www.google.com/settings/ads and opt out of third party networks by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.Security14 Oranges shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural, and technical security with respect to our offices, information storage facilities, and 3rd party cloud based storage services so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.14 Oranges also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users’ trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement14 Oranges reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes to our website home page at www.14oranges.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time 14 Oranges decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.Acceptance of TermsThrough the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use or our Websites. In addition, your continued use of our Websites following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our Websites, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number, or mailing address.Email: info@14oranges.comPhone: 604-304-0020Mailing Address: 210-10451 Shellbridge Way, Richmond, BC, Canada, V6X 2W8Services
Mobile App Development
Apps for Municipalities,Unions & Associations Website Development Web Application Development UI/UX and Design Other Services Customers
Support COPYRIGHT © 2009-202014 ORANGES SOFTWARE INC. PRIVACY POLICY
COPYRIGHT © 2009-202014 ORANGES SOFTWARE INC. PRIVACY POLICY
